allnursingschools.com 2014-12-14

# Privacy Policy

###  Information Collection and Use 

We collect personal contact information ("Contact Information") only if it is entered. The types of Contact Information that may be collected include: name, address, email address, telephone number, fax number and information about your educational interests. This Contact Information is passed on to the schools you identify (sometimes through a vendor that is under contract to the school), so that they may contact you with more information. We may share your Contact Information with our email service provider or business partners who use the data for the purpose of delivering All Star Directories Customer Service and marketing information to you and for other purposes permitted in this Privacy Policy. In addition, we may use your Contact Information to contact you if an inquiry you start on our Website is unable to be completed. Other personally identifiable Contact Information may be shared as required to fulfill your information request or when a business partner provides a product or service that we feel may be of interest to you.

Contact Information is aggregated to create reports on overall education industry trends, which may be sold to third parties. Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. Please note that use of your Contact Information by a school or third party is governed by such school's or third party's privacy policy. You should consult the third party's privacy policy, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

###  Information Sharing 

All Star Directories may share your Contact Information with our service providers who use the information for purposes related to the delivery of marketing and communication materials to our visitors. Every communication we send has links allowing the recipient to unsubscribe or change his or her preferences.

###  Opt-out 

If you receive communications from us or our partners and would like to opt-out of such communications, or would like to opt-out of having your Contact Information shared with a third party business partner, please send us an email at Unsubscribe@allstardirectories.com. Please note that use of your Contact Information by a school or third party is governed by such school's or third party's privacy policy and you will need to separately opt out from that third party's use of such information.

###  Cookies 

To enhance your experience with our Website, many of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your email address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us. In general, All Star Directories uses cookies (small files on your computer) to track Website usage statistics about this Website, to understand where visitors find out about our Website, and to assist in entering data when requesting school information.

###  Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Ad Servers 

When you browse through our Website, we collect information on the efficiency and working of our Website. This includes such information as the number of times a web page is accessed, the browser used, paths taken when moving through the Website, and search terms entered by users. We use this information to improve the operation of our Website. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our Website. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is anonymous information. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp).

###  Schools Contacting You 

Different schools have different methods of following up with student information requests. Some will send brochures in the mail, others will reply via email or try to contact individuals by telephone. By using our service to request information from schools, you are giving permission to schools (or their partners or vendors) to contact you using the method of their choice, to fulfill your information request, notwithstanding your possible listing in the National Do-Not-Call Registry.

###  Privacy Policy Changes 

From time to time, All Star Directories may update this Privacy Policy. You agree to this Privacy Policy, and any changes to the same, by visiting this Website. Therefore, we encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it.

###  All Star Directories 

Finally, if you provide us with your contact information, All Star Directories reserves the right to contact you in the future to help improve our operations, to introduce new services, or provide our partners with customer insights.

We invite you to contact us if you have questions about our Privacy Policy. You may call us at (888) 404-8043 or contact us by mail at the following address:

All Star Directories, Inc.   
2200 Alaskan Way   
Suite 200   
Seattle, WA 98121

Last Modified: September 3, 2008
